Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5149
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Lodge #218- Connellsville, Pa. (Box 83, Folder 19)
- 218 Connellsville, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Lodge #231- McKees Rocks, Pa. (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Lodge #258- East Brady, Pa., 1956-1961 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- 258 East Brady, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Lodge #259- Erie, Pa., 1949 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Lodge #292- Lehighton, Pa., 1961 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- 292 Lehighton, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Lodge #299- Pittsburgh, Pa., 1955-1964 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- 299 Pittsburgh, 1966-1968 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Lodge #309- Pittsburgh, Pa., 1964-1965 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- 309 Pittsburgh, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Lodge #310- Coraopolis, Pa., 1958 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- 337 Sayre, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Lodge #338- Renovo, Pa., 1961-1965 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- 338 Renovo, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- 344 Jersey Shore, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Lodge #345- Freedom, Pa., 1962 (Box 84, Folder 17)
- 345 Freedom, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- Lodge #346- Allentown, Pa., 1952-1961 (Box 84, Folder 19)
- 346 Allentown, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Lodge #382- Avoca, Pa., 1950-1959 (Box 84, Folder 21)
- 382 Avoca-Closed, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Lodge #383- Harrisburg, Pa. (Box 84, Folder 23)
- 386 Johnstown, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 24)
- Lodge #386- Johnstown, Pa. (Box 84, Folder 25)
- 435 Albion, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Lodge #435- Albion, Pa., 1955 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Lodge #442- Scranton, Pa., 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- 442 Scranton, 1967-1968 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Lodge #444- Williamsport, Pa., 1951-1965 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- 444 Williamsport, 1967-1968 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Lodge #447- Monessen, Pa., 1958-1962 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- 447 Monessen, 1967-1968 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Lodge #456- Pitcairn, Pa., 1961-1965 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- 456 Pitcairn, 1966-1968 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Lodge #461- Monongahela, Pa., 1965 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Lodge #462- Punxsutawney, Pa., 1960-1962 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- 462 Punxsutawney, Pa., 1968 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- Lodge #467- Pittsburgh, Pa. (Box 85, Folder 14)
- 467 Pittsburgh, 1960-1968 (Box 85, Folder 15)
- Lodge #476- Pottsville, Pa., 1957-1961 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- 476 Pottsville, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- Lodge #488- Chester, Pa., 1957-1964 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- 488 Chester, 1967-1968 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Lodge #498- Altoona, Pa., 1957-1965 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- 498 Altoona, 1966-1968 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Lodge #511- Philadelphia, Pa., 1959-1962 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- 511 Philadelphia, 1966-1967 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Lodge #521- Sharon, Pa., 1951-1960 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- 521 Sharon, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Lodge #532- Gordon, Pa., 1957 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Lodge #534- McKeesport, Pa., 1957 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Lodge #541- Shamokin, Pa., 1957 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Lodge #544- Wilkes-Barre, Pa., 1961 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- 544 Wilkes-Barre, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Lodge #553- Pittsburgh, Pa., 1956-1962 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- 553 Pittsburgh, 1966-1968 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- 561 Clearfield, 1966-1968 (Box 86, Folder 16)
- Lodge #572- Carnegie, Pa., 1956-1961 (Box 86, Folder 17)
- 571 Carnegie, 1967-1968 (Box 86, Folder 18)
- Lodge #573- Brookeville, Pa., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 19)
- Lodge #574- Harrisburg, Pa., 1957-1965 (Box 86, Folder 20)
- 574 Harrisburg, 1962-1968 (Box 86, Folder 21)
- Lodge #591- Butler, Pa., 1957-1964 (Box 86, Folder 22)
- 591 Butler, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 23)
- Lodge #593- DuBois, Pa., 1960 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Lodge #603- Delano, Pa. (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Lodge #362- Dawson, Pa., 1956-1960 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- 632 Dawson, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Lodge #647- Tamaqua, Pa. (Box 87, Folder 5)
- 665 Pottstown (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Lodge #694- Enola, Pa., 1957-1959 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Lodge #703- Brownsville, Pa., 1955-1958 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Lodge #719- Carnegie, Pa., 1957-1959 (Box 87, Folder 9)
- 719 Carnegie, 1967-1969 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Lodge #734- Pen Argyl, Pa., 1956-1959 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Lodge #742- Blairsville, Pa., 1962-1965 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- 742 Blairsville (Box 87, Folder 13)
- Lodge #753- Freeport, Pa., 1955-1962 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- 753 Freeport, 1966-1968 (Box 87, Folder 15)
- Lodge #771- Mahanoy Plane, Pa., 1957-1958 (Box 87, Folder 16)
- 771 Mahanoy Plane, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 17)
- Lodge #775- Pittsburgh, Pa. (Box 87, Folder 18)
- 775 Pittsburgh, 1967-1968 (Box 87, Folder 19)
- Sanitation Lodge #775 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  Altcoin, Pa. (Closed)
- Lodge #787- Lebanon, Pa., 1954-1962 (Box 87, Folder 21)
- Lodge #808- Pittsburgh, Pa., 1952-1964 (Box 87, Folder 22)
- 808 Pittsburgh, 1967-1968 (Box 87, Folder 23)
- Lodge #862- Newberry, Pa. (Box 87, Folder 24)
- 862 Newberry (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Lodge #863- Pittsburgh, Pa., 1955-1958 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- 863 Pittsburgh, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Lodge #872- Braddock, Pa., 1961-1965 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- 872 Braddock, 1967-1968 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- 872 Braddock, 1967-1968 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Lodge #895- Coatesville, Pa., 1965 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- 895 Coatesville, 1966-1967 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Lodge #948- Pittsburgh, Pa., 1956-1959 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Sanitation- Lodge #954- McKeesport, Pa. (Closed) (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Lodge #953- Philadelphia, Pa., 1952-1964 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- 953 Philadelphia, 1967-1968 (Box 88, Folder 12)
- 954 McKeesport, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Lodge #955- New Castle, Pa., 1953-1965 (Box 88, Folder 14)
- 955 New Castle, 1966-1968 (Box 88, Folder 15)
- Lodge #956- Philadelphia, Pa., 1952-1958 (Box 88, Folder 16)
- 956 Philadelphia, 1966-1968 (Box 88, Folder 17)
- Lodge #978- Philadelphia, Pa., 1955-1962 (Box 88, Folder 18)
- 978 Philadelphia, 1966-1968 (Box 88, Folder 19)
- #989- Bethlehem, Pa., 1958-1964 (Box 88, Folder 20)
- 989 Bethlehem, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 21)
- 997 Braddock, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 22)
- 998 Upper Darby, 1967 (Box 88, Folder 23)
- Lodge #1021- York, Pa., 1958-1963 (Box 88, Folder 24)
- 1021 York, 1966-1968 (Box 88, Folder 25)
- Lodge #1079- Norristown, Pa., 1952-1963 (Box 88, Folder 26)
- 1079 Norristown, 1967 (Box 88, Folder 27)
- Lodge #1092- Pittsburgh, Pa., 1956-1957 (Box 88, Folder 28)
- Lodge #1096- Pittsburgh, Pa., 1953-1962 (Box 88, Folder 29)
- 1096 Pittsburgh, 1967-1968 (Box 88, Folder 30)
- Locomotive Purposes (General), 1963 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Luna, C (President): 1963-1965 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Luna, C (President): 1963-1965 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Luna, C (President): 1968 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Luna, C. (President): 1968 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Luna, C. (President): 1968 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Luna's Statement to Railway Age Weekly, 1963 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Charles Luna (President) 1966-1967 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Charles Luna (President): 1966-1967 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Charles Luna (President): 1966-1967 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Medicare, 1965 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Meeting- Nat'l Conf. of State Legis. Reps., 1930-1949 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Meeting- Nat'l Conf. of State Legis. Rep., 1952 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Meeting- Nat'l Conf. of State Legis. Reps., 1953 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Meeting- Nat'l Conf. of State Legis. Reps., 1954 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Meeting Nat'l conf. of State Legis. Reps., 1955 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Meeting- Nat'l Conf. of State Legis. Reps., 1956 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Meeting- Nat'l Conf. of State Legis. Reps., 1958 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Meeting- Nat'l Conference of State Legis. Reps., 1960 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Meeting- Nat'l Conference of State Legis. Reps., 1962 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Meeting- Nat'l Conference of State Legis. Reps., 1964 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Meeting- Nat'l Conference of State Legis. Reps., 1966 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Meeting- National 30th Convention of B.R.T., 1954 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Meeting- National 29th Convention of B.R.T., 1950 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Meeting- National 31st Convention of B.R.T., 1960 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Meeting- Nat'l 32nd Convention of B.R.T., 1964 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Nat'l 32nd Convention of B.R.T., 1964 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Meeting- National 32nd Convention of B.R.T., 1964 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Meeting- National 32nd Convention of B.R.T., 1968 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Meeting- N.Y. Assoc., 22nd Annual Convention (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Mononghela Connecting Railroad General Grievance Committee (Officers' Meetings), 1963-1964 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Meeting- National Conference of State Legislative Representatives, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Penna. AFL-CIO- First Constitutional Convention, 1960 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  Hilton, Pgh.
- Penna. AFL-CIO- Second Constitutional Convention, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  Sheraton, Phila.
- Penna. AFL-CIO-Third Constitutional Convention, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  Pittsburgh Auditorium, Pgh.
- Penna. AFL-CIO- Fourth Constitutional Convention, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Penna. AFL-CIO- Fifth Constitutional Convention, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Penna. AFL-CIO- Seventh Constitutional Convention, 1966 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Penna. AFL-CIO- Eighth Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Meeting-State-Pittsburgh, 1950 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Meeting-State-Pittsburgh, 1950 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Meeting-State-Harrisburg, 1951 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Meeting-State-Harrisburg, 1951 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Meeting-State-Scranton, 1952 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Meeting-State-Scranton, 1952 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- 1018 Clairton: State Meeting, 1953 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  Philadelphia
- State Meeting: Pittsburgh, 1954 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- State Meeting: Pittsburgh, 1954 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- State Meeting: Williamsport, 1955 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- State Meeting: Williamsport, 1955 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- State Meeting: Scranton, 1958 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Scranton Meeting, 1958 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Harrisburg Meeting, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Harrisburg Meeting, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Harrisburg Meeting, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Harrisburg Meeting, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Pittsburgh Meeting, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Pittsburgh Meeting, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Pittsburgh Meeting, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Philadelphia Meeting, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia Meeting, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Philadelphia Meeting, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Allentown Meeting, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Allentown Meeting, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Allentown Meeting, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Meeting- Pa. State Legis. Bd., 1963 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- General Letters, 1952 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Meeting- Board Material Invitations, 1952 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Representatives Elected in 1951, 1951-1952 (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Reservations, 1952 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Resolutions, Credentials, etc., 1952 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- General Meeting Board Material, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Invitations, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Reservations, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Resolutions, Credentials, Etc., 1956 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Board Meeting- General, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Credentials, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Minutes (Complete Set), 1960 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Resolutions, Etc. (Originals of Material for Minutes), 1960 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Speech (C.J. Sludden), 1960 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Thank You Letters & Telegrams, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Board Meeting (General), 1964 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Board Meeting- (General), 1964 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Committees, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Credentials, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Minutes (Complete Set), 1964 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Resolutions, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Speech (C.J. Sludden), 1964 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Board Meeting (General), 1968 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- Board Meeting (General), 1968 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Board Meeting (General), 1968 (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Committees, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 11)
- Credentials, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Invitations, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Resolutions, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Resolutions, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Merger- AFL-CIO State Council (B.R.T. to Join) (Box 102, Folder 4)
- National Child Labor Committee and Migrant Labor, 1960-1965 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Monthly Statements, 1966-1967 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Monthly Statements, 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Monthly Statements (Penna. State Legis. Board), 1967 (Box 102, Folder 8)
- New York Central System- Lines East General Grievance Committee (Box 102, Folder 9)
- Operating Brotherhoods Protective Association, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 10)
- Passenger Service, 1967 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Pennsylvania Railroad: Operating Revenues for 1967 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Pennsylvania State College, 1960-1965 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- Pennsylvania State College, 1960-1965 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Pennsylvania State College, 1966-1969 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- Pennsylvania State College, 1966-1969 (Box 103, Folder 6)
- Pennsylvania State College, 1966-1969 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Pa. Joint Association Scholarship Fund Committee, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Penn. Joint Association Scholarship Fund Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Penn. Joint Association Scholarship Fund Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Pennsylvania Joint State Association Scholarship Fund, 1963-1965 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Penn. Joint Association Scholarship Fund Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- Penn. Joint Association Scholarship Fund Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 104, Folder 6)
- Penn. Join Association Scholarship Fund Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Pennsylvania Joint State Association Scholarship Fund, 1966-1967 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- College Entrance Exams National, 1963-1965 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- College Entrance Exams National, 1965 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- College Entrance Exams National, 1965-1966 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- College Entrance Exams National, 1966-1967 (Box 106, Folder 2)
- College Entrance Exam Materials, 1968-1969 (Box 106, Folder 3)
- College Entrance Exams National, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Quarterly Reports to Co-Op Leg. Com., 1964-1965 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Quarterly Reports to Co-Op. Leg. Com., 1964-1967 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Quarterly Reports (Penn State Legis. Bd.), 1965 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Quarterly Reports (Pa. State Legis. Bd), 1965 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Quarterly Reports B.R.T., 1965-1968 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Quarterly Reports B.R.T., 1966-1968 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Quarterly Reports B.R.T., 1966-1968 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Quarterly Reports B.R.T., 1966-1968 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Quarterly Reports B.R.T., 1966-1968 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- Rail Commuter Service-Philadelphia, 1961-1963 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Rail Labor (Committee of Pa.), 1962-1965 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Rail Labor (Committee of Pa.), 1966-1967 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Railroad Accident Investigation Report, 1951-1969 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Railroad Safety (Union Calendar No. 632), 1966 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- R.L.E.A., 1959-1966 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Re-Apportionment, 1964 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- Re-apportionment- Ohio, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Report- Board of Directors- B.R.T., 1952-1962 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Report- Board of Directors- B.R.T., 1952-1962 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Report- Board of Insurance- B.R.T., 1953-1959 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Report- Board of Trustees- B.R.T., 1953-1962 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Report- Emergency Board- B.R.T.1955-1957 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Representation Dispute, 1965 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Erie-Lackawanna Railroad- Representation Dispute, 1965 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Right to Work, 1962-1965 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Right to Work, 1962-1965 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Right to Work, 1962-1965 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Booklets, Etc. (Sanition) [sic], 1954-1961 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  Sanitation.
- Booklets, etc. (Sanitation), 1954-1961 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- Cabooses I, 1955-1961 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Cabooses I, 1955-1961 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Cabooses I, 1955-1961 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- Caboose I, 1955-1961 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- Cabooses I, 1955-1961 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- Caboose Material (B&O R.R.- Hennemuth Trainman News), 1961 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Cabooses II, 1961-1962 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- Cabooses II, 1961-1962 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- Cabooses II, 1961-1962 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- Cabooses III, 1963-1964 (Box 113, Folder 7)
- Cabooses IV, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Cabooses IV, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 2)
- Cabooses IV, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 3)
- Cabooses IV, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 4)
- General Letters (Sanitation), 1951-1955 (Box 114, Folder 5)
- General Letters (Sanitation), 1956-1964 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- General Letters (Sanitation), 1956-1964 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- B.L.F. & E Lodge- Conway Yard, I.R.R., 1958 (Box 115, Folder 3)
- B. & O.R.R.- General Letters, 1960-1965 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- B.L.F. & E.- Riker Terminal, Buffalo Div., Baltimore & Ohio R.R., 1958 (Box 115, Folder 5)
- C.R.R. of N.J.- General Letters, 1957-1962 (Box 115, Folder 6)
- D. & H. R.R.- General Letters, 1960 (Box 115, Folder 7)
- Erie- General Letters, 1958-1962 (Box 115, Folder 8)
- L.V. R.R.- General Letters, 1961-1963 (Box 115, Folder 9)
- N.Y.C. R.R.- General Letters, 1957-1962 (Box 115, Folder 10)
- P. & L.E. R.R.- General Letters, 1957-1964 (Box 115, Folder 11)
- P.R.R.- General Letters, 1957-1964 (Box 115, Folder 12)
- Reading. R.R.- General Letters, 1955-1965 (Box 115, Folder 13)
- Reading. R.R.- General Letters, 1955-1965 (Box 115, Folder 14)
- See, Harry (Nat'l & Legis. Rep.), 1960-1961 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- See, Harry (Nat'l Legis. Rep.), 1960-1961 (Box 116, Folder 2)
- Sluden, C.J. (Personal), 1965 (Box 116, Folder 3)
- Sluden, C.J. (Personal), 1965 (Box 116, Folder 4)
- Sluden, C.J. (Personal), 1965 (Box 116, Folder 5)
- Sludden, C.J. (Personal), 1965 (Box 116, Folder 6)
- C.J. Sludden (Personal), 1965 (Box 116, Folder 7)
- Sludden, C.J. (Personal), 1966 (Box 116, Folder 8)
- Sludden, C.J. (Personal), 1966 (Box 116, Folder 9)
- Sludden, C.J. (Personal), 1967 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- Sludden, C.J. (Personal), 1967 (Box 117, Folder 2)
- Sludden, C.J. (Personal) 1967 (Box 117, Folder 3)
- Sludden, C.J.- Salary Increase, 1952-1956 (Box 117, Folder 4)
- Election of State Legislative Representative by Referendum, 1963 (Box 117, Folder 5)
- Strike Benefit Fund, 1960-1961 (Box 117, Folder 6)
- Time Slips, 1962-1965 (Box 117, Folder 7)
- Time Slips, 1962-1965 (Box 117, Folder 8)
- Trainmen's Political Education League, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- Train Men's Political Education League, 1966-1968 (Box 118, Folder 2)
- Trainmen's Political Education League, 1966-1968 (Box 118, Folder 3)
- Trainmen's Political Education League, 1966-1968 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- Trainmen's Political Education League, 1966-1968 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- Unemployment, 1958-1962 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Unemployment, 1958-1962 (Box 119, Folder 2)
- Unemployment Compensation, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- Unemployment Compensation, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Wage and Rules Dispute, 1962-1963 (Box 119, Folder 5)
- Wage & Rules Dispute, 1962-1963 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- Wage and Rule Dispute, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 1)
- Wage and Rules Dispute, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 2)
- Wage and Rule Dispute, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 3)
- Walsh vs. B. of R.T., 1955-1958 (Box 120, Folder 4)
- Weil, W.J. (Gen. Sec.-Treas.), 1950-1954 (Box 120, Folder 5)
- Weil, W.J. (Gen. Sec.-Treas.), 1956-1957 (Box 120, Folder 6)
- Weil, W.J. (Gen. Sec.-Treas.), 1958-1960 (Box 120, Folder 7)
- Weil, W.J. (U.R.O.C.), 1952-1956 (Box 120, Folder 8)
- Western Pennsylvania Asso. Of Lodges, 1964 (Box 121, Folder 1)
- Wible C.E. -Chm., G.G.C., B.R.T. P.R.R.- Lines East, 1963-1967 (Box 121, Folder 2)
- Workmen's Compensation (Booklets), 1954-1962 (Box 121, Folder 3)
- Workmen's Compensation (Booklets), 1954-1962 (Box 121, Folder 4)
- Workmen's Compensation, 1953-1962 (Box 121, Folder 5)
- Workmen's Compensation (General Letters), 1955-1956 (Box 121, Folder 6)
- Workmen's Compensation, 1953-1962 (Box 121, Folder 7)
- Crew Consists (Work Rules), 1964 (Box 121, Folder 8)
- Work Rules, 1962-1964 (Box 121, Folder 9)
- Albert D. Brandon, Esq. (Box 122, Folder 1)
- Communications- Agreements, Press Releases, Statements (Box 122, Folder 2)
- Communications- Congressional Records and Court Cases (Box 122, Folder 3)
- Conflict of Interest (Box 122, Folder 4)
- Delaware River Port Authority (Box 122, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence, Pt. 1 (Box 122, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence, Pt. 2 (Box 122, Folder 7)
- General Correspondence, Pt. 3 (Box 122, Folder 8)
- ICC Finance Dockets 21989, 21990 (Box 122, Folder 9)
- ICC Finance Dockets 21989, 21990-- Pt. 2 (Box 122, Folder 10)
- Merger- Penn Central Merger Compensation (Box 122, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous (Box 122, Folder 12)
- Publications, Pt. 1 (Box 122, Folder 13)
- Publications, Pt. 2 (Box 122, Folder 14)
- Statistics (Box 122, Folder 15)
- Primary Endorsements, 1958 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- General Election Endorsements, 1958 (Box 123, Folder 2)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1960 (Box 123, Folder 3)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 4)
- General Election Endorsements, 1964 (Box 123, Folder 5)
- General Election Endorsements, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 6)
- General Election Endorsements, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 7)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1950 (Box 123, Folder 8)
- General Election Endorsements, 1956 (Box 123, Folder 9)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 10)
- General Election Endorsements, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 11)
- General Election Endorsements, 1950 (Box 123, Folder 12)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1942 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  May 19, 1942
- General Election Endorsements, 1942 (Box 123, Folder 14)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1944 (Box 123, Folder 15)
- General Election Endorsements, 1944 (Box 123, Folder 16)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1946 (Box 123, Folder 17)
- General Election Endorsements, 1946 (Box 123, Folder 18)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1948 (Box 123, Folder 19)
- General Election, 1948 (Box 123, Folder 20)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1954 (Box 123, Folder 21)
- General Election Endorsements, 1954 (Box 123, Folder 22)
- General Election Endorsements, 1934 (Box 123, Folder 23)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1936 (Box 123, Folder 24)
- General Election Endorsements, 1936 (Box 123, Folder 25)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1938 (Box 123, Folder 26)
- General Election Endorsements, 1938 (Box 123, Folder 27)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1940 (Box 123, Folder 28)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1932 (Box 123, Folder 29)
- General Election Endorsements, 1932 (Box 123, Folder 30)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1934 (Box 123, Folder 31)
- General Election Endorsements, 1926 (Box 123, Folder 32)
- General Election Endorsements, 1924 (Box 123, Folder 33)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1930 (Box 123, Folder 34)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1928 (Box 123, Folder 35)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1912 (Box 123, Folder 36)
- Primary Election Endorsements, 1914 (Box 123, Folder 37)
- 1955 Session- Big Truck Bill HB-1390 (Box 123, Folder 38)
- 1951 Session- Big Trucks Bill S.B. 615 (Box 123, Folder 39)
- Truck Case- I.C.C. Riss & Co. Extension- Explosives (Box 123, Folder 40)
- 1953 Session- Big Truck Bill S.B. 804, S.B. 829 (Box 123, Folder 41)
- General Election, 1952 (Box 124, Folder 1)
- Primary Election, 1952 (Box 124, Folder 2)
- General Election, 1953 (Box 124, Folder 3)
- Primary- 1954 (Endorsements Letters and Answers) (Box 124, Folder 4)
- Primary- 1954 (Final File- No. of Printed Copies, etc.) (Box 124, Folder 5)
- Primary- 1954 (General Correspondence) (Box 124, Folder 6)
- Primary- 1954 (Regional Meetings) (Box 124, Folder 7)
- General- 1954 (Authorization and Time Slips) (Box 124, Folder 8)
- General- 1954 (Endorsement Letters and Answers) (Box 124, Folder 9)
- General- 1954 (Final File- No. of Printed Copies, Etc.) (Box 124, Folder 10)
- General- 1954 (General Correspondence) (Box 124, Folder 11)
- General- 1954 (Inauguration) (Box 124, Folder 12)
- General- 1954 (Paper Clippings, etc. from Counties' Reps.) (Box 124, Folder 13)
- General- 1954 (Regional Meetings) (Box 124, Folder 14)
- General- 1954 (Thank-you Letters) (Box 124, Folder 15)